The Imperial Clan Court's Archive Pavilion.
The last files my father reviewed
are right there.
Mr. Shen.
My mother was a distant branch of the royal family.
I visited the Imperial Clan Court with her when I was young.
I remember the Archive Pavilion is in the northeast courtyard.
It's a three-story wooden building.
There is an old guard named Zhao San at the west corner gate.
He slacks off and dozes off every night at midnight.
Miss Gu.
Can you remember anything else?
Like,
the interior layout.
Inside the pavilion,
there's a portrait of Xiao Chong'an in the northwest corner.
My father once said
that Lord Xiao was proficient in feng shui and mechanisms.
If he hid something,
it must be out of sight.
Out of sight.
The northwest corner,
the portrait.
Help me hold him.
We must find a way to break the contract as soon as possible.
The Imperial Clan Court.
We'll go tonight.
You guys stay here
and wait for my news.
Tung oil.
The oil stains are fresh.
Someone has been here recently.
Someone.
They are also looking for something.
Mechanism wires.
They trigger upon touch.
Brother Xiao,
you still like playing these tricks.
Nephew Shen,
since you're here,
why not show yourself and talk?
Good tactics, Lord Qin.
You're even familiar
with the mechanisms set by Lord Xiao.
Brother Xiao and I were once from the same sect.
Nephew,
you've been investigating all along,
isn't it just for the truth?
Your father, Shen Qingshan,
didn't disappear seven years ago.
Instead, he took the initiative to infiltrate them,
using himself as bait
to set up this trap.
The three copper coins are three keys.
Only by collecting them all can you open
the map to the Tianji Pavilion
and find the ultimate answer.
About your father's whereabouts,
about the whole truth of the Dragon Vein Soul Eater.
Why should I believe you?
Just based on this
secret letter your father entrusted me to keep
the night before he disappeared.
He said,
'If Mo insists on tracking this down,
then tell him about this letter
and the secret of the copper coins.
Whether it's a blessing or a curse,
he will choose for himself.'
Mo.
Seeing this letter is like seeing me.
My journey is dangerous.
If I can't return,
you should look for clues of the three coins
and go straight to the Tianji Pavilion.
On the ninth floor of the Black Tower in the Directorate of Astronomy,
lies the answer I left for you.
Way.
The sons of the Shen family
Justice.
must live for truth and justice.
Last words of Qingshan.
Even if what you say is true,
why did you aid the wicked
and hunt down the investigators?
Because their eyes
are everywhere.
If I didn't put on this act,
how could I gain their trust?
How could I survive until today
to give you this letter?
When the three coins unite,
the Tianji Map will appear.
We are still missing my father's
Shen copper coin.
The third Shen copper coin
is right here in the Imperial Clan Court.
It is directly related to
your father's disappearance.
Think about it.
What does the last place your father appeared
have to do with the Imperial Clan Court?
The case files.
Before his disappearance,
the last thing my father requested
was the Imperial Clan Court's sealed file
on the former Directorate of Astronomy's
Director's sudden death.
By the oral decree of His Highness the Crown Prince,
seal the Imperial Clan Court!
Arrest the trespasser
and thief of secrets, Shen Mo!
The Crown Prince's men are here.
I cannot be exposed.
Go quickly, I'll see you at the Tianji Pavilion.
Registrar Shen.
His Highness the Crown Prince requests your presence.
After you.